字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
为了阻止邪恶极速者萨维塔
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
我不小心闯入了未来
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
看到他杀死了我心爱的女人
and I saw him murder the woman that I love.
但是我不会再让这事发生了
But I won't let that happen.
我会尽我一切的努力
I'm gonna do everything in my power
来改变未来
to change the future,
而我是唯一来得及拯救她的人
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
我就是  闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
我把魔法石丢到神速力里之后
hen I threw the Philosopher's Stone into the Speed Force,
我偶然地跑入了未来
I accidentally ran into the future.
我看到萨维塔杀了你
I saw Savitar murder you.
-你要怎么跟爸爸说呢  -我不会说的
- How are you gonna tell Dad? - I'm not.
如果你俩有什么问题
If you guys got something going on,
我希望你能和我聊聊
I hope you know you can talk to me.
每晚我要入睡的时候
Every night when I go to bed,
我都害怕自己醒来后会变成她
I'm afraid that I'm gonna wake up and be her.
我不想要这些能力
I didn't ask for these powers,
就和你不想被萨维塔利用一样
just like you didn't ask to be used by Savitar.
所以你是说每次我昏迷过去
So you're telling me that every time I'm blacking out--
你就化身成了炼金术师
You've become Alchemy.
炼金术士可以恢复人们在闪点的超能力
Alchemy can restore the powers that people had in Flashpoint.
炼金术师的所为不是你的错
What Alchemy did was not your fault.
我是说与他接受训练的这个节点相比
I'm saying that at this point in his training,
-你比巴里快  -什么
- you're faster than Barry! - What?
我这么短时间能达到  这很疯狂
It's crazy how fast I've gotten in such a short time.
我需要你再加快更多
And I'm gonna need you to get a lot faster.
不是我从萨维塔手中拯救爱瑞丝
I'm not gonna save Iris from Savitar.
而是你
You are.
-就是这个  -是的
- So this is it, huh? - Yeah.
那就是我们赛跑的起点
This is the starting line to our race.
西斯科沿着这条跑道上装满了传感器
Cisco set up sensors all along the course,
他会从全程追踪你的速度
and he'll be tracking your speed all the way to the finish line
从起点到城市的另一头
on the other side of town.
不  我是说这是
No, I meant this is it--
在极速者的历史上最闹心的一天了
the day the greatest upset in speedster history goes down.
沃利  输赢并不重要
Wally, man, this isn't about winning or losing.
好吗
Okay?
重点是训练
This is about training
这样你就能变得更快
so you can get faster
从而打败萨维塔拯救爱瑞丝
and beat Savitar and save Iris.
-没错  我一定会的  -好
- Yeah, which I'm gonna do. - Okay.
但我要先把你甩在后面
But first I'm gonna make you eat my dust.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好吧  你知道他们称我为
Okay, you know there is a reason they call me
世界上最快的人是有原因的
the fastest man alive.
西斯科  好了吗
Cisco, you good?
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
中城极速者大赛即将开始
the Central City Speedster 500 is about to begin.
但首先  我压五比一几率
But first, I've got five-to-one odds
巴里战胜沃利
Barry takes down Wally.
-还有下注的吗  -有
- Any takers? - Yep.
竞猜游戏吗  我们是打赌吗
Game of speculation? Are we--we're betting?
有  我要参加
Yeah, no, I'm in.
在我的地球上  是不允许赌钱的
On my Earth, financial wagering was banned
因为副总统艾尔·卡彭遭遇了不幸
after an unfortunate incident with Vice President Al Capone.
你走运了  你现在生活在这里
Well, lucky for you, you live here now.
-是的  -我压20块巴里赢
- Yes. - Put me down for 20 for Barry.
乔  你一定要下注  来嘛
Joe, got to be in it--come on.
不  不了
No, not me.
这是个苏菲的选择  我才不要
That's a Sophie's Choice I'm not gonna make.
压80块巴里赢
$80 on Barry.
老娘需要一个新的共聚焦显微镜
Mama needs a new confocal microscope.
好吧  HR  你的小命掌握在我的手中了
All right, H.R., you put your life in my hands,
我知道你喜欢高风险
so I know for a fact you like high stakes.
你下多少钱
How much you in for?
华莱士最近的速度测试表示他很稳
Wallace's recent speed tests ensure that he is a lock.
我压一张亚伯·林肯
Put me down for an Abe Lincoln.
-什么  -100块
- Hm? - Uh, 100.
不管地球上100块是什么  给我压上
Whatever 100 is on this Earth, put me down for that.
-伙计们  我们准备好了  -好的好的
- Guys, we're ready. - All right, all right.
都下好注了  祝大家心想事成
All bets are in, and may the odds be ever in your favor.
先生们  开启你们的引擎
Gentlemen, start your engines.
-预备  -准备好了
- Ready? - Get set.
跑
Go.
第一个标记点  全程三分之一处
At the first marker, 1/3 of the way in,
第一名
第二名
闪电侠
闪电小子
闪电侠暂时领先  还是闪电小子
Flash is in the lead-- or is that Kid Flash?
是闪电小子  加油  小约瑟夫  加油
Kid Flash! Come on, little Joseph, go.
加油  我需要买双新鞋
Come on, mama needs a new pair of shoes.
加油  华莱士  飞奔吧
Come on, Wallace, down the lane!
我觉得他之前肯定赌过
I think he's done this before.
闪电侠
闪电小子
第二个人标记点  沃利领先
Ooh, second marker. Wally's in the lead.
太好了  沃利  真是我的好儿子
Yeah, Wallace! That's my boy!
-是我儿子  -是你儿子
- You mean that's my boy. - That's your boy.
我要下双份
I want to double down.
我现在要下双份
I want to double down on that right now.
HR  大金主
Oh, H.R., big spender.
-你认真的吗  -认真吗
- You serious? - Serious?
我认真得心脏病都要发了  财主
Serious as a heart attack, Rich.
闪电侠
闪电小子
大伙  他们不分上下
Guys, they're neck and neck.
快到终点了
And almost at the finish line.
太好了
Yes!
-给钱  -来吧
- Pay up. - Hmm?
现在吗
Now?
能赊账吗
Do you guys take IOUs?
得了吧  这不算
Come on, man, that didn't count.
你知道我现在还不能穿墙
You know I can't phase yet.
伙计  你刚不是看见我做到了吗
Man, you just saw me do it, right?
你必须得面对前进道路中的
And you have to be ready to face any obstacle
一切障碍
that's put in your path.
别担心  巴里
Yeah, well, don't worry, Barry.
我会更快的
I'ma get faster.
很快我就会比你还快了
Pretty soon I'm gonna be faster than you.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
在那之前  我的名字是什么
Well, until then, what's my name?
闪电侠
第三季
第十二集
路易餐厅
乔  这具尸体
Joe, hey, this one, is, uh--
非常吓人  警探  我提醒你
Pretty ghastly, Detective, I warn you.
-这就是尸体吗  -是的  怎么了
- That's the body? - Yeah, why?
因为他死了不到八小时
Because he died less than eight hours ago.
八小时
Eight hours?
他是这里的厨师
He was a chef here--
他叫斯图尔特·霍尔兹曼  餐厅老板确认
Stuart Holzman -- and the owner confirmed
他昨晚在这上班
that he was working last night.
短时间内造成的损失不小啊
That's a lot of damage in a short amount of time.
他会是超能力者吗
We thinking he's a meta?
有可能  虽然某些化学物质
Possibly, although certain chemicals
会引起类似的反应
can cause a similar reaction.
任何酸碱值低于2的强酸都会
Yeah, any acid with a pH below two.
没错
Precisely.
我们有可能面对的是一种
We could be looking for an aggressive variant
具有侵略性的坏死筋膜炎变体
of a necrotized fasciitis.
一种噬肉菌病
A flesh-eating disease.
在餐厅里吗
In a restaurant?
我再也不外出吃饭了
I'm never eating out again.
尸检也许能帮我们搞清楚
Okay, so an autopsy might help us hone in
是什么东西导致这样的
on what really did this.
我同意
Yes, I agree.
可惜我向市里申请3D图像医学扫描仪
Unfortunately, County denied my request
他们拒绝我了
for a 3D image medical scanner,
不然就能在短时间内完成尸检了
which would make short work of the process.
尖端科研实验室有一台
Okay, well, we have one at S.T.A.R. Labs.
艾伦  这可是正在调查的案件
Allen, this is an active investigation.
我们要遵循规定
There is protocol to follow...
这点是肯定的吧
surely?
除非我们想查出这是什么东西
Not if we're gonna figure this out.
好吧  我会亲自装好尸体  在那汇合
Okay, I'll bag the body myself and meet you there.
好
Great.
爱瑞丝
Iris.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  我只是
Yeah, I'm just, uh,
交稿期限快到了  所以...
running up against a deadline, so...
既然你们俩都在  我想问问
Since I have you both, I wanted to ask,
塞西尔的女儿琼妮
um, Cecile's daughter, Joanie,
来了市里  所以我在想
is in town, and I was thinking
也许我们可以一起见个面
that maybe we could all get together.
如果你们觉得进展不会太快的话
If you don't think it's too soon.
毕竟我和她交往的时间也不久
I mean, I haven't exactly been dating Cecile for that long.
不会太早的  乔
It's not too early, Joe.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
吉特咖啡店可以吗
And Jitters-- is that cool?
还是说太随便了
Or is that too casual?
爸  别担心
Dad, don't worry, okay?
这很好  琼妮会很喜欢你的
It's great. Joanie's gonna love you.
爱你们  我的孩子
I love my kids.
我去约她们  谢谢
I'm gonna set it up. Thank you.
没事
All right.
看到他这么开心真好
It's nice to see him so happy.
是的
Yeah, it is.
你没事吧
You okay?
在尖端科研实验室  我有东西要给你看
I need to show you something at S.T.A.R. Labs.
好
Okay.
路易餐厅
尖端科研实验室
市政厅
之后
你看
Look.
那是我们刚刚去过的餐厅
That's the name of the restaurant where we just were.
-是的  -我和老板聊过
- Yeah. - I spoke to the owner,
他说他认为那家餐厅遇到这种事
and he said he doesn't think that the restaurant can survive
名声应该毁于一旦了  他们几乎认为
an attack like this-- that they'd most likely
要以新名字重新再开一家才行
have to reopen under a new name.
-一切都应验了  巴里  -不
- It's all coming true, Barry. - No.
我以为事情会有所改变
I thought things were changing.
事情的确正在发生变化
Things are changing, okay? They are.
我本来应该阻止掠夺的
I was supposed to stop Plunder, right?
结果沃利阻止了他
And instead Wally did.
我们也会
And we're gonna...
阻止萨维塔的  我一定会确保这点
stop Savitar too. I'm making sure of it.
如果我们无法阻止这一切呢
What if we can't stop all of this?
我很害怕  巴里
I'm scared, Barry.
那好吧
Okay, uh...
也许我们应该和乔说
Maybe we should tell Joe.
不行
No, no.
不行  我们说好不告诉他的
No, we agreed that we wouldn't.
而且  你之前也看到他
Besides, you saw him earlier.
正在规划与塞西尔的未来
He's-- he's planning for a future with Cecile.
如果我们把萨维塔的事告诉他
If we tell him about Savitar,
他会不顾一切地来帮我
it's all he's gonna think about.
我不能这么对他
I-I can't do that to him.
-我不会的  -好吧
- I won't. - Okay.
你想怎样都行
Whatever you want.
听我说
Now listen to me.
我向你保证我会竭尽全力
I promise you I'm doing everything in my power
保证那个未来不会发生
to make sure that that future never happens.
好
Okay.
你觉得《犯罪现场调查》里的角色是这样的吗
You think this is what it's like to be a character on "CSI"?
他们希望从检验中获得些什么呢
What do they hope to gain from that examination?
他们想找出致死原因
They're trying to find the exact cause of death.
一旦查出致死原因  我们就能更好
Once we know that, we'll have a better idea
应付我们所面对的事物
of what we're dealing with.
但在那之前  我们需要培训
But until then, we need to train.
我会把我所知道的全都教给你
I'm gonna teach you everything I know,
从穿越墙体开始
starting with phasing.
-终于轮到这个了  -知道我们该做什么吗
- Yes! Finally. - You know what we should do?
我们应该编制一些模拟
We should concoct some simulations
来帮助华莱士学到这个新能力
to help Wallace learn this new skill.
你觉得如何  弗朗西斯科
What do you say, Francisco?
我对此只有一个回答
I got one word for you:
白坚木
quebracho.
走吧
Let's go.
白坚木
Quebracho!
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
现在已经无所谓了  不是吗
Doesn't really matter much now, does it?
当然有所谓  在经历了这么多之后
Of course, we should call him by his name.
我们应该称呼他的本名
After everything he's been through,
这是他应得的尊重
he deserves that much respect.
他是个尸体
He is a corpse,
因此不太受医生对病人的态度影响
thus impervious to such bedside manners.
那真是感谢上苍了  我真不忍心
Well, thank goodness, 'cause I'd hate to have
让他忍受你的摆布
to subject him to yours.
受害者是男性  30到40岁之间
Victim is male, between 30 and 40,
有着高度的表皮坏死
with a highly necrotized epidermis.
我们准备做个全身检查
We plan to do a full-body scan
并进行胸壁内收缩
and a chest wall retraction.
朱利安  快看
Julian, look.
腐烂在细胞死亡后还在继续
The decay continues even after the tissue's dead.
这不是细菌
This is--this is not a bacteria.
或是任何医学上熟知的疾病
Or any other disease known to medical science.
刚才那场可真棒  老兄
That was one crazy set, man.
我跟你说  罗伯  你萨克斯管这么吹下去
I'm telling you, Rob, you keep wailing on that saxophone,
没多久你就能赶上李·杰伊·汤普森了
you're gonna running up to Lee Jay Thompson in no time.
好了  玩得高兴  之后见
All right, have a good one. Catch you laters.
好的
All right.
-我认识你吗  -不太可能
- Do I know you? - Unlikely.
但我知道你  胡里奥·门德斯
But I know you, Julio Mendez.
老兄  刚才那场太棒了
Man, that was some set.
你演奏的那首《巴的码头》
Your cover of "Dock of the Ba"
带我进入了另一个时空
took me to a different time and place.
我很高兴你喜欢演出  老兄
Well, I'm glad you dug the set, man.
那个  在你走之前
Hey, before you go, uh,
我非常想和你握握手
I'd just really like to shake your hand.
行啊  粉丝的要求一定实现
Yeah, anything for a fan.
你对我做了什么
What'd you do to me?
是你对我造成的痛苦相应的惩罚
What you deserve for all the pain you caused me.
这痛起来像是...
That hurt like a...
像是撞上了大木头墙吗
Like you ran into a giant wooden wall?
因为就是如此
'Cause you did.
而且不是普通的大木墙
And it's not just any big wooden wall.
是双重加固的白坚木
That's double-reinforced quebracho.
那个可是星球上最坚硬的玩意
That's like the strongest stuff on the planet, right there.
选得真是妙  西斯科
Well, fantastic choice, Cisco.
本来是木头是铁还是石头都无所谓
Well, it shouldn't matter if it's wood or steel or stone.
只要你移动的够快  你就能穿过任何东西
If you're moving fast enough, you can phase through anything.
即便是熔岩也行
Even molten lava--
你知道  如果你掉入了火山的话
you know, if you ever ended up in a volcano.
我还是搞不明白
You know, I-I still don't get it.
-你是怎么做到的  -好吧
- How do you do this? - All right.
来  看好了
Here. Watch.
当你的震动和空气的自然频率相同时
When you vibrate at the natural frequency of air,
你的身体  你的细胞  就会处于激发状态
your body, your cells, will be in an excited state
这样你就可以
that'll allow you...
穿越物体
to phase.
好吧  这个没有什么帮助
Yeah, it's not-it's not really helping.
我具体的要怎么做
What exactly do I do?
感受你的身体  好吗
Connect with your body, right?
感受空气  成为纯粹的电
Connect with the air. Be pure electricity.
你要感觉你周围的一切
You have to feel everything that's around you.
好吗
All right?
加速然后感觉万物
So go fast and feel things.
好吧  不用担心
Yeah, no worries.
你能做到的  华莱士
You can do this, Wallace.
好吧
Okay.
好的  好的
All right, all right.
你能做到的
You can do this.
好了  再来
All right, again.
-好吗  -你能行的
- Yeah? - You got this.
这不行  根本不行
This isn't working. It's not working.
你一直在训练他  要怎么办
You've been training him. What's worked?
你知道要怎么对付这家伙吗
You know what works with that guy?
诚恳的鼓励  你能行的  华莱士
Vocal encouragement. You got this, Wallace!
我都不知道你问他干什么
I don't know why you even ask him.
威尔斯对我是怎么做的
What did Wells do with me?
他精心筹划过的计划
His plan was, uh, more methodically constructed
可比《七宗罪》里的约翰·杜还完整
than John Doe's in "Seven""
并且他可有更多的时间来准备
And he had a bit more time to work it out
估计前后有个十五年吧
by, give or take, 15 years.
我们可没有十五年的时间
Well, we don't have 15 years.
有罪案发生了  我得走了
I have a crime scene. I got to go.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
让他一直进行练习
Just make sure he keeps practicing.
冲啊  华莱士
Go, Wallace!
尸体是被那个骑行者发现的
Body was found by that bicyclist.
和第一起的犯罪手法相同
Same M.O. as the first one.
这个受害者昨晚在这里表演
This victim was performing here last night.
他是一名酒吧歌手  名叫胡里奥·门德斯
He's a lounge singer named Julio Mendez.
胡里奥·门德斯
Julio Mendez?
有谁见到韦斯特警探了吗
Has anybody seen Detective West?
在闪点里  他是门德斯警长
In Flashpoint, he was Captain Mendez.
抱歉  在闪点  这个你曾经生活过的
Sorry. In Flashpoint, this-this alternate universe
平行宇宙中  他是中城警局的一员吗
that you lived in, he worked at the CCPD?
是的
Yeah.
等等  另一个受害者  斯图尔特·霍尔兹曼
Wait a second, the other-the other vic, Stuart Holzman--
咱们有他的照片吗
do we have a photo of him?
-有  -我能看看吗
- Yeah. - Can I see it?
等一下  就是他
Yeah, hold on. That's him.
怎么了
What is it?
他也是那里的警察
He was a cop there, too.
所以这是第二个闪点里警察被杀了
So this is the second dead cop from Flashpoint?
是的
Yeah.
咱们得找出这家伙是谁
We got to figure out who this guy is.
如果我们抓紧时间  还有机会
Well, if we hurry, there's still a chance
我们可以在他尸体分解之前
we can get some of the attacker's
得到凶手残余的DNA
residual DNA before this corpse disintegrates,
但我们得快点
but we've got to move quick.
巴里  这你帮得上忙
Barry, you can help with that.
好的  走吧
All right, come on.
有人看到我了吗
Did anybody see me?
天啊  我都差点没看到你
Damn, I barely saw you.
我们得走了
Look, we got to get going.
乔  等等
Hey, Joe, hold on.
我知道你很激动
Um, look, I-I know how excited you are
我们要跟琼妮和塞西尔喝咖啡什么的
for this coffee thing with Joanie and Cecile,
但我觉得我们应该推迟一下
but I think we should hold off.
我觉得现在这么做不好
I don't think it's a good idea right now.
巴仔  这两起袭击并不算是有规律可循
Bar, these two attacks don't establish a pattern.
-可是  -再说了  我是警察
- Well... - And besides, I'm a cop.
如果每次我有危险就取消计划
If I canceled my plans every time I was in danger,
那我就出不了门了
I'd never leave the house.
你说得对
I-I hear you.
我只是确保你安全
I would just feel a lot better
才会觉得安心
knowing you were someplace safe.
你说说还有哪个地方
Name a place safer than a coffee shop
比我和两个极速儿子在一起的咖啡厅更安全
with my two speedster sons.
见琼妮对塞西尔很重要
Meeting Joanie is important to Cecile,
因此对我也很重要
therefore it's important to me.
有些事情值得去冒险
Some things are worth taking risks for.
好吧  我们走吧
All right. Let's get out of here.
发现什么了吗
Anything?
除了这个尸体
Aside from this body
正当着我们的面分解以外吗
disintegrating before our eyes?
没什么异常的了
Nothing unusual.
这些坏死组织肯定有一个最严重地方
There must be a heightened point of necrosis somewhere.
听着
Look!
在这个尸体像之前那个分解成灰之前
We have less than 50 minutes before this corpse disintegrates
我们还有五十分钟
into ash like the last one.
-我们必须现在找出来  -我知道
- We need to find it now. - I'm aware.
如果我一个人做的话可能会更快
This might be a faster process if I did it alone.
要知道  我做过尸检的  朱利安
You know, I've done autopsies before, Julian.
我相信你做过
I'm sure you have.
只是如果我一个人做的话
This might just be a quicker process
可能会更快
if I did it alone.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
他手掌心那里
The gradation is darker
和人有接触
on the palm of his hand
看起来颜色更深
from the point of contact.
是啊  是啊
I see, I see.
以前巴里抱怨和你共用实验室的时候
You know, I used to think Barry was overreacting
我还觉得他是反应过激了
when he complained about sharing a lab with you.
但现在我算是理解他的苦了
But now I understand his frustration.
相信我  没人比我更苦了
Believe me, no one is more frustrated than I.
你知道你是可以做到不每时每刻
You do realize that it's possible not to be a jerk
都当个混蛋的  对吧
all the time, right?
对对对
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
正在扫描
人类
超能力者
两株DNA
Two strains of DNA.
其中一株一定是凶手的
One of them must be from our killer.
超能力者DNA数据库
但是这里面有其他东西
But, you know, there's something else here.
其中一株DNA里有一个元素
One of the DNA strains has an element in it.
你之前看到过类似这样的东西吗
Have you ever seen anything like that before?
看到过
I have--
在炼金术师制造的超能力者外壳里看到的
in all the meta husks created by Alchemy.
这意味着杀了两个无辜市民的超能力者
Which means the meta that killed our two innocent people...
是我造就的
was created by me.
吉特斯咖啡店
-塞西尔的法式烘焙咖啡  -谢谢
- French roast for Cecile. - Thank you.
琼妮的无奶绿茶拿铁
Non-dairy green tea latte for Joanie.
你不怎么喝咖啡吗  琼妮
You not much of a coffee drinker, Joanie?
我以前喝  但后来我得知
Well, I used to be, but then I learned
高温烘焙的咖啡豆
hot roasted coffee beans contain
含有大量致癌物质丙烯酰胺
cancer-causing levels of acrylamide.
我的妈
Well, damn.
琼妮  塞西尔说你在海滨大学
Uh, Joanie, Cecile says you're at Coast U?
-你是学什么的  -我还没决定
- What are you studying? - I'm undecided.
那你有大体方向吗
Are you leaning towards anything?
并没有
Not really.
海滨大学挺远的  对吧
Uh, Coast U's pretty far, right?
你不想念中城吗
Do you ever miss Central City?
其实我更喜欢那里
Actually, I like it better there.
不过有一点我很想念中城
Well, there is one thing I miss about Central City.
是什么
What's that?
你会后悔你问了的
You're gonna regret that you asked.
闪电小子
Kid Flash.
她有点  有点着迷
She's a little-- little obsessed.
你想念中城就只想念闪电小子
Kid Flash is the one thing you miss about Central City?
巴里  慢着
Whoa, Barry, slow down.
你不用这么怀疑吧
You don't have to be so skeptical about it.
闪电小子多酷炫
Kid Flash is cool.
具体来说  你最喜欢他哪一点呢
What do you like best about him, specifically?
他很无惧
Well, he's fearless.
-他很勇敢  -对
- And he's brave. - Yeah.
他是个英雄  而且说不定面具下的他也挺可爱
He's a hero, and he's probably pretty cute under that mask.
我也这么觉得
Yeah, I think so, too.
得了吧  琼妮  闪电小子
Come on, Joanie, honey, Kid Flash?
他就爱炫耀  又是自拍
He's a showboat-- he's snapping selfies,
又是在建筑上留闪电涂鸦
he's leaving graffiti bolts on buildings.
-那是他的标志动作  -那算是他的标志动作
- Okay, that's his signature move. - That's kind of his signature.
但是据我所知
Yeah, well, from what I hear,
闪电侠才真正拯救生命的那个
The Flash is the one who's actually saving people.
听起来塞西尔是站闪电侠队了
Sounds like Cecile's Team Flash.
琼妮
Uh, Joanie,
我爸爸从来不吹嘘这个
my dad would never brag about this,
但是他认识闪电小子
but he knows Kid Flash.
真的吗
You do?
那我妈妈说的对吗
Is my mom right?
谁才是真正的英雄
Who's the real hero--
闪电侠还是闪电小子
Flash or Kid Flash?
他们俩都是...
Mmm... they both are.
他们俩都对中城做出了很大贡献
Uh, they both do great things for Central City.
好吧  那如果你一定要选呢
Okay, but if you had to choose?
我不...
I-I don't--
我觉得我选不出来
I don't think I could choose.
必须选一个呢
Yeah, but if you, like, had to.
你能帮我加点奶吗  沃利
Um, would you go get me some cream, Wally, please?
好的
Yes.
工作的事  我马上回来  抱歉
Ah, this is work. I'll be right back, sorry.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
巴里  我们在门德斯的尸体上
Barry, we got some DNA
发现了一些DNA
off Mendez's corpse.
和中城警局的记录对比之后发现
We were about to match it with CCPD records.
那个超能力者叫克莱夫·约金
The meta's name is Clive Yorkin.
我们现在把他的信息发给你
We're sending you his info now.
乔·韦斯特警探
Detective Joe West!
好久不见
Long time, no see.
我认识你吗
Do I know you?
你不记得我了
You don't remember me?
你和你的好友们以前以毁我生活为乐
You and your cronies had a very fun time ruining my life.
这次你可做不到了
Not gonna let you do that this time around.
我想你找错人了
I think you have the wrong guy.
不  不
No, no.
你就是我记忆中的乔·韦斯特
You're the Joe West I remember.
虽然看上去更有活力一点
Look a lot more full of life now, though.
但别担心...
But don't worry...
我会帮你改变的
I can change that.
-都往后退  -琼妮  快走
- Everybody get back. - Joanie, go.
大家都出去  快走  快走
Everybody get out of here. Everybody go! Go!
都跑吧
Yes, everybody run.
吉特斯咖啡店
我只要他
I only want him.
你在上面可藏不住  警探
You can't hide up there, Detective.
如今没人能从我手里逃脱
No one can hide from me anymore.
-乔  -再往前走我就开枪了
- Joe... - One more step, and I'll shoot.
之前就没用
Didn't work then.
现在也没用的
Won't work now, either.
我说了
Told ya.
停下
Stop!
你可不能碰我  极速者
Can't touch me, speedster.
我就知道  闪电小子才是最棒的英雄
I knew it. Kid Flash is the hero.
还好有闪电小子在  对吧
Well, thank God for Kid Flash, huh?
他走了
He's gone.
DNA扫描结果
克里夫·约金
这个人摸到的都会死
This guy's got the touch of death.
没错  而且不仅仅是杀人
Yeah, he does, and it's not just people.
他触碰到的任何东西都会变成灰烬
Anything he touched turned to ash.
乔  我真的觉得你应该呆在这里
Joe, I--I really think you should just stay here
直到我们找到约金
until we find Yorkin.
不行  我要去看看塞西尔和琼妮
No, I'm gonna go check on Cecile and Joanie.
她们被吓坏了
They were pretty shook up.
爸爸  你疯了吗
Dad, are you crazy?
这个人想杀你
This guy wants to kill you.
要是沃利和巴里不在的话  他就得手了
If it wasn't for Wally and Barry, he could've.
我们都有可能被他杀掉
He could've killed any one of us.
我们遇到过比约金更厉害的超能力者
Come on, we have been through much worse metas than Yorkin.
怎么了
What?
爱瑞丝  我没事  我们都没事
Iris, I'm fine. We're all fine.
我们今天都好好的
We're not losing anybody today.
可能今天没事  但不久就会
Maybe not today, but soon.
不久
Soon?
你在说什么
W-what are you saying?
爱瑞丝...
Iris...
沃利  他需要知道
Wally, he needs to know.
需要知道什么
Needs to know what?
当巴里把魔法石
When Barry threw the Philosopher's Stone
扔进神速力的时候
into the Speed Force,
发生了一场爆炸
there was an explosion,
他被推进了未来世界
and he was propelled to the future.
未来
The future?
是几个月之后
It was a few months from now.
他看见他自己
What he saw was himself
站在萨维塔...
standing before Savitar...
还有我的面前
and me.
之后萨维塔就杀了我
Right before Savitar killed me.
你是说几个月后...
So you're saying that in a few months...
你会死
you die?
除非我们能改变未来  爸爸
Unless we can change the future, Dad.
而我们正准备这么做  乔
Which we're gonna do, Joe, okay?
我不...  我们不会让这件事发生的
I'm not--we're not gonna let this happen.
你们知道这事多久了
How long have you known about this?
多久
How long?
几周了  乔
A couple weeks now, Joe.
你们现在才告诉我
And you're just telling me now?
那是我的女儿
That's my daughter!
爸爸  我不让他们说
Dad, I didn't want them to say anything
是因为我知道你会如何反应
because I knew how you would react.
这种事你不该瞒着你爸爸  爱瑞丝
This is not something you keep from your father, Iris!
你应该知道的
You should've known that.
-你也应该知道  -我懂  乔
- And you should've too. - I know, Joe.
我能理解他们为什么不告诉我
Look, I can understand why they didn't want to tell me
因为他们没有和我在同一屋檐下长大
because they didn't grow up under the same roof
你不一样
that you did.
他们不知道我的宝贝女儿对我的意义
They don't know--they don't know what my baby girl means to me,
巴里  但你知道
Barry, but you do.
我知道
I know.
乔...
Joe...
我去跟他聊聊
I'll talk to him.
我要去中城警局
I'm--I'm gonna go to CCPD,
看看能不能找到抓住约金的线索
see if I can find anything that might lead us to Yorkin.
那真是顺利
Well, that went swimmingly.
乔是对的  我们应该早点告诉他
Joe's right. We should've told him before now.
你该告诉他的是  这事应该怪我
What you should have told him is that I'm the one responsible,
那个要杀他的超能力者是我创造的
that the meta trying to kill him is one that I created.
朱利安  你没法改变已经发生的事情
Julian, you can't change what happened to you.
那不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你总是这么说  但那就是我的错
You keep saying that, but it is my fault.
人总要为自己的行为负责
People are responsible for their own actions.
矢口否认只是...
To say otherwise is just...
只是为了让自己好受点
it's just a way to make yourself feel better.
你就是这么看我的吗
Is that what you think I'm doing?
认为我在为自己做过的事找借口
Making excuses for things I've done in the past?
你知道吗  我真的开始后悔
You know, I'm really starting to regret
带你加入了
bringing you in here.
路易餐厅
接啊  爸爸
Come on, Dad.
爸爸  是我
Ah, hey, Dad, it's me...
我又打来了
calling, again.
我知道你很生气
Look, I know you're upset,
但还是给我回个电话吧  好吗
but, um, give me a call back, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
路易餐厅出现超能力者
亲爱的
Honey?
晚上好  爱瑞丝·韦斯特
Good evening, Iris West.
是爱瑞丝的紧急呼救
It's Iris's panic alarm.
她在公寓  我联系巴里
She's at the apartment. I'll call Barry.
不用  不用  我能搞定
No, no, no. I-I got this.
他在中城警局  我更近
he's at CCPD, and I'm closer.
好  去吧
Okay, go!
你知道吗  起初  我想要你爸爸死
You know, initially, I wanted your dad dead.
可接着我想  如果我真想让他痛不欲生
But then I thought, "If I really want to make him suffer,
我该杀了他女儿
I should kill his daughter instead"
我不该这么死
This is not how I'm supposed to die.
我确定就是这样
Oh, I'm pretty sure it is.
不  住手
No, stop!
太晚了  闪电小子
Too late, Kid Flash.
我还是她
Me or her?
有我在  宝贝女儿
I've got you, baby girl.
我哪也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
心跳加速  体温104华氏度
Elevated heart rate. Temperature's 104.
腐烂已经扩散到皮下组织了
The decay is reaching her subcutaneous tissue.
我来了  怎么回事
I'm here, all right? What happened?
约金突袭了她
Yorkin went after her.
怎么没联系我
Why didn't you call me?
因为当时我在
Because I was here.
那也应该联系我
You call me! All right?
我们得用点什么
We have to give her something.
一定有什么可以给她用
There has to be something we can give her.
不是细菌引起的
It's not bacteria.
抗生素没用
Antibiotics won't work.
我们得想办法
We have to do something.
不能坐以待毙
Nothing's not an option.
对了  如果香蕉熟得太快  该怎么做
Okay, what do you do when a banana ripens too quickly?
-把它放进冰箱  -妙极了
- Put it in the freezer. - That's brilliant.
凯特琳  你可以把她的手臂冻住
Caitlin, you can freeze her arm.
这样就能阻止腐烂扩散
It'll stop the spread of decay
为我们寻找解药争取时间
and give us some time to find a cure.
我相信你
I trust you.
我做不到  即便我很想
I can't, even if I wanted to.
这不是吹一股冷风就好了
We're not talking about a cold blast.
而是要持续不断地输送冷气流
This is a specific and continuous cold stream.
温度高了  腐烂会继续扩散
Too high a temperature and the decay spreads,
温度低了则会造成冻伤  破坏神经末梢
too low and the frostbite will destroy your nerve endings.
而且持续使用超能力那么久
And that long using my powers,
我可能会失控
I could lose control.
凯特琳  你很坚强  明白吗
Caitlin, you are strong, okay?
比你想象的更坚强
Stronger than you know.
你不会失控的
You are not going to lose control.
凯特琳  试试吧  拜托了
Caitlin, try, please.
起作用了
It worked.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
-你还好吗  -目前还好
- You okay? - So far, so good.
沃利  你去哪
Wally, where are you going?
离远点  这样我就不会再搞砸了
Out of the way where I can't screw up again.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
听着  我刚才说的...
Hey, look, what I said back there--
不  你说得对
No, you were right.
我们应该联系你的
We should've called you.
我只是以为...我以为我能行
I just thought-- I thought I could do it.
我以为我准备好了  但显然没有
I thought I was ready. Obviously, I'm not.
那不能怪你
It's not on you.
我还不够快  巴里
I wasn't fast enough, Barry.
这完全该怪我
That--that is totally on me.
不  其实不是
No, not really.
不怪你  好吗
It's not, all right?
我刚刚获得超能力时  我...
Look, when I got these powers, I-I...
我真的很幸运  虽然这么说比较别扭
I was really lucky, in a weird way.
有很多人帮我一起渡过了那个阶段
You know, I had a lot of people helping me through all of this.
有两个威尔斯
I had Wells--both of 'em--
还有杰和佐勒蒙
and Jay and Zolomon.
虽然他们当中有两人成了坏蛋
I mean, two of them turned out to be bad guys,
但他们还是良师
but even they were good teachers
教会我如何运用超能力
who really taught me how to use my powers.
我只是觉得  我还没为你做到这样
I just don't think that I've been that for you yet.
你已经把我需要学的都告诉了我
You're telling me everything that I need to learn.
我只是还没学会  我...
I'm just not getting it. I--
不  不是这样  而是...我...
No, that's not it. It's--I've been--
我一直在让你发挥自己的原始技能
I've been letting you coast by on your raw talent,
你的底子很好  但传授远远不只是
which you have a lot of, but teaching--it's a lot more than
做一些示范  就指望你自己学会
just doing something and expecting you to follow.
而是需要启发你
It's about inspiring and
赋予你力量  让你利用自己的天赋
empowering you to use your gifts
靠自己去成功
to succeed on your own.
那才是我需要做的
That's what I need to do.
从现在开始  我就要这么做
That's what I'm gonna do from now on.
下一次  你独自面对敌人的时候
So the next time you're out there and you're alone,
你一定会赢
you will win.
说好了
Deal?
Deal.
HR和我刚刚想到一个办法
H.R. And I just came up with a way
找到约金  但这方法很
to track down Yorkin, and it's...
疯狂
crazy.
挑战时空级别的疯狂
Like, defies time and space crazy.
好吧  先说我们知道的
Okay, here's what we know.
我们知道约金的目标是闪点里的警察  对吧
We know Yorkin's going after cops in Flashpoint, right?
但我们不知道具体是谁
What we don't know is who he's going after.
但如果我们找出他们是谁
But if we find out who they are,
我们就能准备好对付他了
then we can be ready for him.
对  那我们怎么做到呢
Right, so how do we do that?
我们用震波感应闪点
We vibe Flashpoint.
闪点已经不存在了
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore.
打断你一下  BA
Stop you right there, BA.
闪点在这个宇宙不存在了
Flashpoint doesn't exist anymore in this universe.
但在量子力学里
But in quantum mechanics,
-子代宇宙原理告诉我们   -宇宙原理
- the daughter universe theory tell us-- - Universe theory.
你所做的每个决定
For every decision you make,
都对应一个你不存在于其中的宇宙
a universe exists where you don't.
对  那堂课我真去上了
Yeah, I actually went to that class.
你最好每堂课都去上
You better be going to all your classes.
所以如果有一个你留在闪点的平行宇宙
So if there is a universe where you stay in Flashpoint,
弗朗西斯科可以用震波感应它
Francisco here could vibe it.
你确定你能做到吗
And you're sure you can do that?
不  不  一点都不
No, no. Not at all.
但吉普赛说过  我能用我的能力做一些
But Gypsy did say I could do some pretty incredible things
-很不可思议的事  -是啊  她说了
- with my powers... - Yeah, she did.
一些我还没意识到的事
Things I'm not even aware of yet, so--
甚至我想象不到的事
things I haven't even imagined.
-好吧  那我们开始想象吧  -好的
- Well, let's get to imagining. - All right.
你们需要我做什么
What do you need me to do?
我只需要你站在这儿
All I need you to do is to stand there,
把注意力集中到闪点  好吗
focus on Flashpoint, okay?
集中到中城警局  乔和曼德斯那部分
Focus on CCPD, Joe, Mendez, that part of it, and
其他的都交给我
I'll take care of the rest.
成功了
It worked!
我到这里了
I'm here.
不知为何  我以为闪点看起来会很不一样
For some reason I thought Flashpoint would look a lot different.
好吧  如果我是乔·韦斯特
Okay, all right, if I were Joe West,
我会在哪儿呢
where would I be?
他还在同一个工位
He was at the same desk.
找到你了
Got ya.
如果不是因为这次追捕
If it wasn't for this takedown,
我们这番对话就会大不相同了  乔
we'd be having a different conversation right now, Joe.
明白  队长
Understood, Captain.
乔有麻烦了
Ooh, Joe's in trouble.
女士们先生们  今天的游街示众
Ladies and gentlemen, for today's perp walk,
我们找到了真正的人渣
we have a literal degenerate:
独一无二的克莱夫·约金
the one and only Clive Yorkin.
好戏登场
Here we go.
曼德斯队长  韦斯特警探
Captain Mendez, Detective West,
谢谢你们的协助
thanks for the assist.
这暴徒被捉拿归案  你们俩功不可没
Couldn't have bagged this goon without you.
把他关到铁山监狱
Get him to Iron Heights.
斯通
是斯通
Stone...
-谁是斯通  -斯通是另一个警察
- Who's Stone? - Stone--that was the other cop.
我告诉你  她可喜欢让罪犯游街示众了
And let me tell you, she loves her perp walks.
劳拉·斯通  她是个私家侦探
Laura Stone. She's a PI.
对  就是她
Yeah, that's her.
当时是你  曼德斯  霍尔兹曼和她
It was you, Mendez, Holzman, and her.
你们在闪点中抓捕了约金
You guys took down Yorkin in Flashpoint.
好吧  那说明她是目前唯一
Well, then, that means she's the only one
还没被约金找上的人了
that Yorkin hasn't gone after yet.
把最好的留在最后  真经典
Classic example of saving the best for last.
我这就着手处理  你们留在这儿想想
I'm on it. You guys stay here and try to figure out
如何抓住一个我们碰不了的人
how to catch somebody we can't touch.
-乔·韦斯特  好久不见  -你好
- Joe West. Long time, no see. - Hey.
我真希望这次见面是在更好的情况下
I wish it were under better circumstances.
听着  你被一个超能力者盯上了
Listen, you're being targeted by a meta.
亲爱的  往那边瞧
Sweetheart, take a look over there.
我是这里唯一盯梢的人
I'm the only one doing the targeting here.
那女孩的丈夫要付我
That chick's husband is paying me
两倍的佣金  快走开别碍事
twice my going rate, so scram.
你看这个
Look at this.
那个盯上你的人
The guy that's coming after you
碰你一下就能把你变成这样
can do that with one touch.
全体旅客请注意
Attention, all passengers.
尖端科研城市快车各站台现在开始上车
The S.T.A.R. City Express is now boarding all platforms.
不如多任务同时进行吧
How about we multitask?
请旅客们上车
All aboard, please.
朱利安
Hey, Julian.
有什么进展吗
You have anything?
听着  现在说还为时尚早  但
Look, it's early days, but...
第一批测试结果显示她的血液
first tests show that her blood
正在攻击她身体里的细胞
is attacking the cells in her body.
等一下  那和我的血液
Wait, that's the opposite of how my blood
导致细胞再生恰好相反
causes cells to regenerate.
正是如此
Precisely.
能用我的血来救她吗
Can we use my blood to save her?
听着  我不认为你的血
Listen, I don't think that your blood
是救爱瑞丝的关键所在
is the key to saving Iris.
但我认为它可能正是我们
But I do think it might be exactly what we need
打败约金所需要的
to take down Yorkin.
希望尚存  伙计
All is not lost, mate.
-腐烂还在扩散  -为什么
- The decay is spreading. - Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
凯特琳
Caitlin?
-凯特琳  -我要失控了
- Caitlin? - I'm losing control.
好吧  腐烂在扩散了
Okay, all right, it's spreading.
我们需要你
We need you.
没事的  会好的
Hey, it's okay. It's okay.
再持续一段时间她就会死的
Just a little bit longer, and she's dead.
这样改变未来怎么样
How's that for changing the future?
我知道你是谁  凯特琳  你不想这么做
I know who you are, Caitlin. You do not want to do this.
这才是真的我  你说过的
This who I am. You said it.
是时候为自己的行为负责了
It's time for me to take responsibility for my actions.
是时候承认我的本来面貌了
Time for me to own who I really am.
你是凯特琳·斯诺
Who you are is Caitlin Snow.
我能直接感受到你内心的斗争
I know firsthand the battle going on inside of you.
我知道这是什么感觉
I know what it feels like.
发生在我身上的时候  我迷失了
When it happened to me, I lost.
我很脆弱  让它占了上风
All right? I was weak, and I let it win.
而且我对很多好人
And I did-- I did horrible things
做了可怕的事
to a lot of good people.
你没必要这么做
And you don't have to do that.
你不会这么做
You're not gonna do that.
你比我强大  凯特琳
You're stronger than I am, Caitlin.
比我强大多了
You're far stronger than I am.
你是我认识最强大的人之一
You're one of the strongest people I've ever known.
你能赢得这场斗争
You can win this fight.
爱瑞丝现在需要你的帮助
Iris needs your help now.
没事了
It's all right.
会好起来的
It's gonna be all right.
你怎么知道这个人会冲我来  乔
And how do you know this guy's coming after me, Joe?
我们有相当可靠的情报
We have pretty reliable intel.
劳拉  这个人不容忽视
Look, Laura, this is not someone you should be ignoring.
他很危险
He's dangerous.
已经杀害了两个警察
He's already killed two cops.
他还想要杀我和我的女儿
He tried to kill me and my daughter.
我肯定是惹恼过很多人
Well, I've certainly pissed off a lot of people in my day.
但我现在唯一害怕的是忘记清空浏览器记录
But the only thing I fear now is forgetting to clear my browser.
知道了
Consider me warned.
天呐
Oh, my God.
危险警报
乔·韦斯特信号
那是什么
What is that?
是乔的危险警报
It's Joe's panic alarm.
他肯定在那列火车上
He must be on that train.
那火车不可能停...
There's no way that train can stop--
不可能及时停下来
It's not gonna stop in time.
得把所有人救出来
We have to get everyone out of there.
没有足够的时间
We don't have enough time.
-不  -怎么回事
- Oh, no! - What is it?
-所有人做好防护  -怎么了
- Everybody brace yourselves! - What's happening?
我们得移动火车
We're gonna move the train.
怎么做
How are we gonna do that?
我去振动它
I'll vibrate it.
我会把它振动得足够快  让它穿过去
I'll vibrate it fast enough that it can phase through this.
-能做到吗  -我不知道
- You can do that? - I don't know.
我从未试过
I've never tried before.
大家坚持住
Everybody hold on!
有可能吗
Is that even possible?
我们会知道的
We're about to find out.
太酷了
Holy Kardashians.
巴里  巴里
Barry. Barry!
没事了
We're good, man.
累坏我了  但成功了
Took a lot out of me, but it worked.
也许是  但我们有新问题了
Yeah, maybe, but we got another problem.
约金回来了
Yorkin's back.
你知道他们是怎么说的  闪电小子
You know what they say, Kid Flash.
如果第一次不成功  再试一次
If at first you don't succeed, try, try again.
你得阻止他
You have to stop him.
我现在精疲力尽了
I don't have it in me right now.
我需要你把血注入他体内
I need you to get your blood into him.
这会中和他的细胞  让他的超能力失效
It'll counteract his cells and negate his powers.
碰都碰不到他  我该如何去做
How am I supposed to do that when I can't even touch him?
你得穿过他
You're gonna phase it into him.
你知道我从未做到过
You know I've never done that before.
你刚刚看着我做了一件从未做过的事
And you just watched me do something I'd never done,
但我还是做了  因为我别无选择
but I did it because I had to.
好吗
All right?
我知道你可以的  好吗
I know you can do it, okay?
我需要你也相信自己
I need you to believe it, too.
跑吧  沃利
Now run, Wally.
跑
Run.
成功了
It worked!
-我做到了  -你的确做到了
- I did it! - You sure did.
再见  闪电小子
Good-bye, Kid Flash.
看看啊
Oh, wha--look at that.
你的超能力失效了  约金
Your powers are neutralized, Yorkin.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我赢了
I won.
爱瑞丝
Iris.
爸爸
Dad?
我上一次这么欣喜地望着你
The last time I was this happy looking in your eyes,
是你刚出生的时候
you'd just been born.
没事了
It's okay. You're okay.
约金被解决掉了
Yorkin's done.
发生了什么事
What happened?
我来告诉你
I'll tell you what happened.
华莱士太厉害了  就是这么着
Wallace was a total badass. That's what happened.
解释一下
Translate.
他把自己的极速者血液
Yeah, he phased his speedster blood
注入约金体内  中和了他的超能力
into Yorkin and neutralized his powers.
这就是背后的科学
That's the science behind it.
我有个很棒的老师
I had a great teacher.
那我呢
And me?
约金的血液稳定下来时
Once Yorkin's blood was stabilized,
我们就成功得到了治愈你的解药
we actually managed to get an antidote that cured you.
你得戴着绷带过几天
You'll have to wear the bandage for a few days,
但除此以外  你完全康复了
but other than that, you're absolutely recovered.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我知道你为我冒的险
I know what you risked for me.
有人帮了我一把
I had some help.
这可没法独自完成
Couldn't have done it alone.
这是团队协作的结果
It was all of us working together.
真为大家感到骄傲
Yup, really proud of everybody.
干得好  今天真棒
Great job. Big ideas today.
我是说  如果我们要从萨维塔手中救下爱瑞丝
My point is, if we're gonna save Iris from Savitar,
我们得更强大
we're gonna have to up our game.
不再有隐瞒
No more lies--
即便是出于善意
even well-intentioned ones.
我们必须对彼此完全坦诚
We have to be completely real with each other.
-我赞成  -我也赞成乔说的
- I agree. - I agree with Joe, too.
从现在开始  完全坦诚
From here on out, complete honesty.
坦诚
Honesty.
好好休息  好吗
All right. Get some rest, all right?
我待会儿再来看你
I'll check on you in a bit.
-巴仔  -怎么了
- Bar? - Yeah?
萨维塔预言有个人会死
Savitar's prophecy of someone dying--
是爱瑞丝吗
was it Iris?
是的
Yeah.
但这件事不会发生的
But it's not gonna happen.
我很高兴她现在是你生命中的第一位
Look, I'm glad she comes first in your life now.
要跟我女儿在一起
If you're gonna date my daughter,
就该这么做
that's the way it should be.
你还是紧随其后的
You're still a close second.
好暖心
It's just heartwarming.
真的好暖心
It's just truly heartwarming.
你已经在为你的书
You're already crafting a version of this
编写这一段了  对吗
for your book, aren't you?
"家族韦斯特终于得到平静"
"Peace finally descends upon the family West"
韦斯特家族  还是家族韦斯特
The West family, or family West?
好  我要去工作了
Right, it's time I get to work.
这么晚还工作
At this hour?
是的  外头还有个超能力外壳
Yes, there's still one husk meta out there,
我要把他找出来
and I intend to find him.
晚安
Good night.
朱利安
Hey, Julian?
我不会因为
I don't think you're weak
你和萨维塔的事觉得你很弱
because of what happened to you with Savitar.
让我稳定下来的力量
The strength that I found to stay in control--
是你给我的
that came from you.
谢谢你
So thank you.
我没打算让爱瑞丝
Well, I wasn't gonna let Iris
死在冰霜杀手的手里  对吗
die at the hands of Killer Frost, was I?
我知道你的内心有善良的一面
I knew there was a good guy inside of you somewhere--
我们都希望你能多展现这一面
one that the rest of us would like to see a little more often.
晚安
Good night.
你想去喝一杯吗
Do you want to get a drink?
什么  现在吗
What? As in now?
是的
Yeah.
好啊好啊  我很乐意
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'd love that.
中城警局
怎么到我这大开间的小角落来了
What brings you to my neck of the bullpen?
琼妮要回去参加期中考了
Oh, Joanie's headed back for midterms.
所以我们过来跟你道别
We just thought we'd come and say good-bye.
我想再跟你们喝咖啡去
I was hoping a redo on the coffee,
因为上次搞砸了
seeing as how the last one went off the rails.
怎么会
Are you kidding me?
我能近距离见到闪电小子行动
I got to see Kid Flash in action, right up close.
我们有很多闪电小子的故事
Well, we got a lot of stories about Kid Flash
我保证你没有听过
I can guarantee you've never heard.
也许下次你来市里
Maybe we can tell you them over dinner
我们可以在晚饭时说给你听
next time you come to town.
我下个月有长周末
I have a long weekend next month.
你确定你要承诺
You sure you're ready to commit to something
那么久之后的事吗
that far in the future?
我当然确定
I am absolutely sure.
很好
Good.
我们得走了
We should go.
-上学顺利  -谢谢  再见
- Good luck at school. - Thank you. See ya.
-再见  宝贝  -再见
- Bye, babe. - Bye.
好  像新的一样好
Okay, good as new.
其实  比新的还好
Actually, it's better than new
我多加了三个锁
with the three extra locks that I added.
你不用那么做
Which you didn't have to do.
西斯科有提过要帮我们做一扇
Well, Cisco did offer to build us
定制安全门
a custom security door,
我们都看过那些东西
but we've both seen how well
如何让人远离尖端科研实验室
those things keep people out of S.T.A.R. Labs.
-那么  -我喜欢门栓
- So... - I like deadbolts.
门栓好用
Deadbolts work.
因为这里刚出了事
It's just with... what happened here,
我想让你有安全感
I want to make sure you feel safe.
我有
I do.
对一切都是吗
About everything?
这几周你一直说
You know, you've been saying for weeks
你一定会从萨维塔手里救下我
that you were gonna save me from Savitar.
虽然我可以把生命托付给你
And while I trust you with my life,
我还是很难不感到害怕
it was hard not to feel scared.
有时我觉得我男友
You know, sometimes it feels like The Flash is this guy
跑去救别人时才是闪电侠
my boyfriend becomes when he runs off to save other people.
好像闪电侠属于大家  但不属于我
Like I'm the only one who doesn't get The Flash.
感觉他跟你不是一体的
He felt separate from you.
但昨天你救我时
But yesterday when you saved me,
我知道我根本不用害怕
I remembered that I have no reason to be scared.
我爱的男人是个超级英雄
The man I love is a superhero.
我爱你  相信你  巴里·艾伦
I love and trust you, Barry Allen...
闪电侠
The Flash.
我爱你们大家  永远不变
I love all of you, and I always will.
我爱你
I love you.
这样真好
That was so nice.
杰西
Jesse!
不不不不
No, no, no, no.
怎么了
What's wrong?
古鲁德
Grodd.
抓走了我爸爸
He's got my dad.
他把他关在猩猩城
And he has him in Gorilla City.